AGU JOE CHUKWUEBUKA

PERSONAL STATEMENT

A Frontend Developer Transforming Concepts into Seamless User Experiences using HTML, CSS, TAILWIND, JAVASCRIPT, REACT and NEXT.JS. Experienced in social media managing and audience engagement with a good background as a personal assistant with exceptional organizational skills and attention to detail, making me suited to develop user-friendly and intuitive web interfaces

WORK HISTORY

PERSONAL ASSISTANT AND PURCHASING
 MANAGER 2015 – 2017

Personal assistant to the director of Emart supermarket Lagos and also doubles as the purchasing manager of the supermarket

• PERSONAL ASSISTANT 2017 -2019

Personal assistant to the director of Hilly pharmaceuticals

PERSONAL ASSISTANT AND IT PERSONNEL
 2021 – 2024

Personal assistant to the principal officer EMEKA NWOSU AND CO chambers, also doubling as the IT personnel of the law firm

5 Tatiye street off Berger Quarry,
Mpape Abuja



08165069358



devleoncode@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Data Trending Knowledge
- Web development
- CCTV Technician
- Solar inverter Technician
- Self-motivated Professional
- Versatility
- Team Player

EDUCATION

BSc Information Technology – In view

META Front-end Developer Certificate

UDEMY Front-end Developer Certificate